http://www.exedy.co.uk/privacy

New to Range - Stage 1 Organic Plus
The Difference Between OE and "OE Quality"
Privacy Policy
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors.  This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on our site) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Exedy Clutch Europe Limited of Unit 2 Rokeby Court, Manor Park, Runcorn, Cheshire WA7 1RW.
(1)      Credit
This document was created using an SEQ Legal template.
(2)      What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:
(a)      Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation.
(b)      Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site and information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services.
(c)      Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us.
(3)      Cookies
Cookies will be dealt with as per our Cookies Policy.
(4)      Using your personal information
Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
(a)      Administer the website
(b)      Improve your browsing experience by personalising the website to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
(c)      To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
(d)      Enable your use of the services available on the website
(e)      Send to you Products purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website.
(f)          Send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you.
(g)         To notify you about changes to our service.
(h)         To provide third parties with statistical information about our users - but this information will not be used to identify any individual user.
(i)           Deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.
(j)          Keep the website secure and prevent fraud.
(k)         To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
(l)           If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.
(m)        If you are a new customer, we will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.
(n)         If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the order form) or as set out below.
We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, SagePay.  You can review the SagePay privacy policy at www.SagePay.com.  We will share information with SagePay only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds.
(5)      Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.
In addition, we may disclose your personal information:
(a)      To the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b)      In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c)          In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk.
(d)          To any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.
(e)          We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.
(f)          We may disclose your personal information to third parties:
•        In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
•        If Exedy Clutch Europe Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
•        If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Exedy Clutch Europe Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
(6)International data transfers
Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.
Information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area.
You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted and carried out through our appointed agent through a secure site.
(7)      Security of your personal information
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure password and firewall protected servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to the website).
(8)      Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
(9)      Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you.  Provision of such information will be subject to:
(a)      The supply of appropriate evidence of your identity.
We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by not checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data or by unticking the appropriate boxes below.
You agree that you do not object to us contacting you for any of the above purposes:
by telephone
by SMS
by e-mail
in writing
and you confirm that you do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of your rights under the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003.
You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at enquiry@exedy.co.uk
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
(10)    Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
(11)    Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
(12)    Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please write to us by email to info@exedy.co.uk.
Cookies Policy
Our website uses cookies. We will ask you to consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy when you first visit our website. By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.
(1) Credit
This document was created using an SEQ Legal template.
(2) About cookies
A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.
Cookies can be used by web servers to identity and track users as they navigate different pages on a website and to identify users returning to a website. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.
Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies. A persistent cookie consists of a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, which will be stored by the browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date (unless deleted by the user before the expiry date). A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.
(3) Cookies on this website
We use both session cookies and persistent cookies on this website.
We may send to you the following cookies:
User ID
(4) How we use cookies
Cookies do not contain any information that personally identifies you, but personal information that we store about you may be linked, by us, to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.
We may use the information we obtain from your use of our cookies for the following purposes:
To identify returning visitors to the website
To maintain the shopping cart on the website
To provide analytics
To analyse the use of our website
To trace navigation trails around our website
In the administration of this website
(5) Third party cookies
When you use our website, you may also be sent third party cookies.
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
(6) Blocking cookies
Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. For example:
In Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector;
In Firefox you can block all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Options", and un-checking "Accept cookies from sites" in the "Privacy" box.
Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites. If you block cookies, you will not be able to use the online store on this website.
(7) Deleting cookies
You can also delete cookies already stored on your computer:
In Internet Explorer, you must manually delete cookie files (you can find instructions for doing so at support.microsoft.com/kb/278835)
In Firefox, you can delete cookies by, first ensuring that cookies are to be deleted when you "clear private data" (this setting can be changed by clicking "Tools", "Options" and "Settings" in the "Private Data" box) and then clicking "Clear private data" in the "Tools" menu.
Doing this may have a negative impact on the usability of many websites.
(8) Contact us
This website is owned and operated by Exedy Clutch Europe Ltd. (Company registered no: 2440644)
If you have any questions about our cookies or this cookies policy, please contact us by email to enquiry@exedy.co.uk
Office open hours
MON - FRI: 8:30AM - 5PM
Want to email us?
enquiries@exedy.co.uk
Call us
+44(0)1928 571850
Company Contact Details
EXEDY Clutch Europe Ltd.
Unit 2, Rokeby Court,
Runcorn,
United Kingdom,
Sign up to our newsletter to stay informed on the company's latest news.
Please enter a valid email.
Success, you have been subscribed.
